https://afm.mb.ca/about-afm/privacy-policy/

English
Français (French)
Problem Gambling
Rapid Access to Addictions Medicine (RAAM)
AFM Library
Fetal Alcohol Spectrum Disorder (FASD)
Information that is automatically collected
When you visit our Web site, we collect information that is required for the operation of this Web site. We collect this data for statistical research and analysis of trends so that we know how many people visit our site and when, the geographical region they are from and which pages they view on our site. We also use “cookies”, or small pieces of information that we store on the use of our site to recognize returning visitors and monitor their activity through our site. Cookies identify your computer or electronic device as a unique visitor to our site enabling us to effectively aggregate site usage statistics to improve our website and make it more user friendly.
Collecting personal information to provide requested services
If you contact AFM by email or complete a comment card, you will be providing us with some personal information including your name, email address, and perhaps some information about your personal circumstances. We will use this personal information only to reply to your question or comment and in order to keep statistics about requests for information for statistical research and planning purposes. It will not be disclosed to any other office or individual outside of the Addictions Foundation of Manitoba for any other purpose, except to investigate a crime, an offence or unauthorized, excessive or improper use of this Web site or to comply with an order of a court or other person or entity with authority to order disclosure or Where disclosure is required by law.
Linking to other sites
There are links to other sites from the AFM website pages. The AFM website privacy policy does not extend to any sites that are not maintained by us and beyond our control.
Authority to collect personal information
Our authority to collect this information is section 36(1)(b) of The Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act and/or section 15(1)(a)(b) of The Personal Health Information Act and our mandate under The Addictions Foundation Act to inform the public of Manitoba. Any information collected by AFM will be protected by the provisions of these Acts.
If you have any questions, please contact:
Webmaster – webmaster@afm.mb.ca
Need Assistance?Contact AFMHelp AFMDonate Today
DISCLAIMER: This website provides general information only and is not intended as a substitute for professional advice. Every effort is made to ensure that the information is accurate at the time of posting. The Addictions Foundation of Manitoba is not responsible for and may not be in agreement with information provided by other websites that are linked to this site.
Manitoba Addictions Helpline
1-855-662-6605
24-Hour Problem Gambling Helpline Toll-Free
1-800-463-1554
About AFM
About
Accreditation
Strategic Plan
Rapid Access to Addictions Medicine (RAAM)
Fetal Alcohol Spectrum Disorder (FASD)
